view j/s it's a JavaScript framework for building front-end UIs in view you can
查看 j/s 它是一个用于构建前端 UI 的 JavaScript 框架，您可以
start simple and then progressively add in the tools and features that you need
从简单开始，然后逐步添加
to build a complex web application at its core it provides a way to build
构建复杂 Web 应用程序所需的工具和功能，它提供了一种构建
components that encapsulate data or state in your JavaScript and then
封装组件的方法JavaScript 中的数据或状态，然后
connect that state reactively to a template in HTML we call these
将该状态响应式连接到 HTML 中的模板，我们将这些
components declarative views because the same data inputs will always produce the
组件称为声明性视图，因为当我们在它链接或绑定的此数据对象上声明数据时，相同的数据输入将始终
same output in the visual UI when we declare data on this data object it
在可视 UI 中产生相同的输出
links or binds it to the HTML on the template above when the value of the
当数据的值
data changes the component will automatically rerender or in other words
发生变化时，组件将自动重新呈现，或者换句话说，
it's reactive and the framework does a ton of work under the hood to make sure
它是响应式的，并且框架在后台做了大量工作，以
that this process is performance across a huge component tree we can work with
确保这个过程在巨大的组件树中是性能的
this data in the template thanks to views HTML based template syntax we can
由于视图基于 HTML 的模板语法，我们可以在模板中处理这些数据我们可以
interpolate a value for expression using double braces and we also have a variety
使用双括号为表达式插入一个值，我们也有 有
of directives to control the behavior of the HTML based on the data we can use VF
多种指令来根据数据控制 HTML 的行为，我们可以使用
to only render an element when the value on the right side is truthy and then we
VF 仅在右侧的值为真时呈现元素，然后我们
might have a fallback element after that that's only rendered when the values
可能会有一个后备元素，仅在值时呈现
fall C with V else we can make the app interactive by listening to events using
Fall C with V 否则我们可以通过使用 V on 指令监听事件来使应用程序交互
the V on directive we can listen to an event on an element then run some code
我们可以监听元素上的事件然后在右侧运行一些代码
to handle that event on the right side we can do that directly in the template
来处理该事件我们可以直接在模板中执行此操作
or define a custom method and the components methods object the method has
或 定义一个自定义方法和组件方法对象，该方法可以
access to our reactive data and that means all we have to do is change the
访问我们的响应式数据，这意味着我们所要做的就是更改
value of the data and the component will automatically rerender and that's all it
数据的值，组件将自动重新渲染，这
takes to build an interactive reactive declarative UI component with view the
就是构建交互式响应式声明式 UI 所需要的全部内容 带有视图的组件 该
framework is loved by developers for the simplicity but also its ability to scale
框架因其简单性而受到开发人员的喜爱，而且它能够
up in complexity incrementally its plugin system allows you to easily drop
逐步扩展复杂性，它的插件系统允许您轻松
in things like a router state management firebase support and more and perhaps
放入诸如 路由器状态管理Firebase 支持等等，也许
best of all it's not sponsored by some mega corporation it's not pressured to
最好的是它不是由一些大型公司赞助的，它没有一直
push out new releases all the time and does a great job listening to its
推出新版本的压力，并且很好地倾听了它的
community this has been GU Jas and 100 seconds stay tuned for a full length
社区，这是 GU Jas 和 100秒敬请期待
tutorial here on YouTube in the near future and check out my view firebase
不久的将来在 YouTube 上的完整教程，
course on fire ship if you're ready to start building a full stack app thanks
如果您准备开始构建一个完整的堆栈应用程序，请查看我在 Fire Ship 上查看 Firebase 课程，
for watching and I will see you in the next one
感谢观看，我会在下一个